Today's Big Up goes to all the legendary children, children, children, the legendary children.
Lil Uzi Vert, honey. He just served, bop, Coachella with some fierce voguing.
They gave the crowd some old way, some new way, some dips, and even a death drop, honey.
Okay, I'm going to say that it's a breath of fresh air to see artists like Lil Uzi being their whole authentic selves
and thriving in hip-hop while breaking free from the tied old thug and pimp stereotypes.
Now, for what it's worth, his name is still Lil Uzi Vert, okay?
Don't ever get it tripping. He does have the blicky, okay?
And if he doesn't, JT does.
You better work, darling!
Today's letdown goes to whoever is in charge of the budget for the Philadelphia 76ers Legends statues.
Oh, they did my boy dirty.
As an avid Allen Iverson fan during his heyday, I was not pleased with what he was presented with by his statue.
His statue at the Penn Medicine Philadelphia 76ers training complex, it is deserved,
but it looks small enough to come inside of a Happy Meal.
He's already, you know, of small stature.
I mean, he's not Muggsy Bogues, but God dang.
76ers have their legends looking like action figures.
Like, they're literally like Indian in the cupboard, okay?
Y'all gotta do better.
It's the city of brotherly love. Show these brothers some love, okay?
You can't have a statue of Allen Iverson that's smaller than Allen Iverson.
I mean, that's just, I feel like, the way it should go.
We are, we are, we are.